歌手：Macklemore & Ryan Lewis FEAT. Ray Dalton
压制:随Feng
不可阻挡
Can't Hold Us
So we put ou hands up
所以我们举起双手
Alright,OK,alright OK
Return of the Mack, get up!
Mack归来 来吧
What it is, what it does, what it is, what it isn’t
怎么回事 那是什么 那不是什么
Looking for a better way to get up out of bed instead of
我不喜欢每天清晨起床后第一件事
Getting on the Internet and checking a new hit me
迫不及待上网看谁在黑我
Get up! Thrift shop pimp strut walking, little bit of humble, little bit of cautious
《二手店》让我招摇过市 带点谦逊 带点谨慎
Somewhere between like rocky and Cosby sweater gang nope nope y’all can’t copy
介于小丑和猛男之间 我的格调你们永远无法拷贝
Yup. Bad, moon walking, this here, is our party, my posse's been on Broadway
就像MJ的《Bad》月球漫步 这里就是我们的派对 我的兄弟都在百老汇
And we did it, our way
我们特立独行
Grown music, I shed my skin and put my bones into everything I record to it
做顶级的音乐 我把自己的血肉都倾注到我的音乐里
And yet I’m on
我仍在努力攀登
Let that stage light go and shine on down
让那舞台的聚光灯打在我身上
Got that Bob Barker suit gameand plinko in my style
我的音乐还有Bob Barker的《价格竞猜》节目的调调
Money, stay on my craft and stick around for those pounds
钞票 我能用我的嘻哈技术赚上不少
But I do that to pass the torch and put on for my town
但我玩嘻哈是为了自己的家乡 把火炬传递下去
Trust me. On my I-N-D-E-P-E-N-D-E-N-T shit hustler
相信我 还有我屌爆的独-立-嘻-哈-音-乐
Chasing dreams since I was 14 with the four track bussing
14岁时我就扛着4轨录音机开始追逐梦想
Halfway cross that city with the backpack
背着行囊 穿越半个城市
fat cat, crushing Labels out here
那里有唱片界大佬和大型唱片公司
Now they can’t tell me nothing
但他们无法对我指手画脚
We give that to the people
我们给予粉丝
Spread it across the country
让他们把我们的音乐传播到全国
Labels out here
那里有唱片公司
Now they can’t tell me nothing
但他们不能对我指手画脚
We give it to the people
只有我们的粉丝
Spread it across the country
才能将我们的音乐传播到全国
Here we go back, this is the moment
我们再度归来 就是现在
Tonight is the night, we’ll fight till it’s over
就在今晚 我们要不停抗争
So we put our hands up like the ceiling can’t hold us
所以我们高举双手 无人能阻挡我们
Like the ceiling can’t hold us
无人能阻挡我们
Here we go back, this is the moment
我们再度归来 就是现在
Tonight is the night, we’ll fight till it’s over
就在今晚 我们要不停抗争
So we put our hands up like the ceiling can’t hold us
所以我们高举双手 无人能阻挡我们
Like the ceiling can’t hold us
无人能阻挡我们
Now, can I kick it? Thank you. Yeah I'm so damn grateful
我能开始了吗？ 谢谢 没错 我无比感激
I grew up, really wanted gold fronts
年轻时 我真的很想带上金牙套
But that’s what you get when Wu-Tang raised you
但那是因为你从小就在武当派的熏陶下长大
Y’all can’t stop me, go hard like I got an 808 in my heart beat
无人能阻挡我 我努力奋斗 好像心跳声都成了低音鼓
And I’m eating at the beat like you gave a little speed
我在吞食节奏 就好像《鲨鱼周》节目里
to a great white shark on shark week Raw
下了药后飞速游动的大白鲨
Tell me go up. Gone!Deuces goodbye
飞向太空 消失不见 道声再见
I got a world to see, and my girl she wanna see Rome
我要去周游世界 我的女友想去罗马
Caesar make you a believer. Now I never ever did it for a throne
凯撒会让你相信梦想 但我从未想争名夺利
That validation comes from giving it back to the people
我只是想做出好音乐来回报粉丝
Now sing a song and it goes like
唱一首歌 就象这样
Raise those hands, this is our party
举起双手 这就是我们的派对
We came here to live life like nobody was watching
我们要享受生活 不要在意别人的眼光
I got my city right behind me,If I fall, they got me
全西雅图的粉丝都在我身后 我失败了 他们会支持我
Learn from that failure gain humility and then we keep marching ourselves
从失败中吸取教训 学会谦逊 让我们继续前进
Here we go back, this is the moment
我们再度归来 就是现在
Tonight is the night, we’ll fight till it’s over
就在今晚 我们要不停抗争
So we put our hands up like the ceiling can’t hold us
所以我们高举双手 无人能阻挡我们
Like the ceiling can’t hold us
无人能阻挡我们
Here we go back, this is the moment
我们再度归来 就是现在
Tonight is the night, we’ll fight till it’s over
就在今晚 我们要不停抗争
So we put our hands up like the ceiling can’t hold us
所以我们高举双手 无人能阻挡我们
Like the ceiling can’t hold us
无人能阻挡我们
I saw we put our hands up
我看见我们高举双手
Na na na na na na na na
And all my people say
大家一起唱
Na na na na na na na na
That's right
就这样
And all my people say
大家一起唱
Na na na na na na na na
Go away
直到离开
And all my people say
大家一起唱
Na na na na na na na na
Ma-ckle-more
Let the night come before the fight's won
在战斗胜利之前 黑夜将会降临
Some might run against the test
有时梦想会在黑夜终结
But those that triumph,embrace the fight'cuz
但若要成功 就要勇于拼搏
It be as there to prove that courage exists
因为这样才能证明勇气的存在
Let the night come before the fight's won
在战斗胜利之前 黑夜将会降临
Some might run against the test
有时梦想会在黑夜终结
But those that triumph,embrace the fight'cuz
但若要成功 就要勇于拼搏
It be as there to prove that courage exists
因为这样才能证明勇气的存在
压制:随Feng